[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
[fzzt]
[whimpering]
WHAT THE FUCK?!
WHAT HAPPENED?!
HOW DID YOU TURN INTO THREE PEOPLE?!
WHAT--
SCIENTIST: I hope those people in the
Lambda Lab can get this under control.
GET *WHAT* UNDER CONTROL?! ME?!
I WANT ANSWERS, ASSHOLE!
IS THIS A THOUGHT-EXPERIMENT?!
AM I IN A SIMULATION RIGHT NOW?!
IS THIS DRUG-INDUCED LUCID DREAMING?!
I KNOW I'M NOT DEAD! IT LOOKS
LIKE WITCHCRAFT TO ME!
THIS IS A CABAL!
YOU SUMMONED ME HERE AS
PRACTICE FOR A DEMON, RIGHT?!
SAY SOMETHING!
SCIENTIST: Well, the dimensional breach is
definitely transmitting organic matter.
WHAT THE FUCK?! YOU THINK THIS
IS A SIMPLE EXPERIMENT?!
YOU THINK I'M JUST A TEST SUBJECT?!
WELL, I KILLED YOUR LEADER!
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?!
YOU'RE DEALING IN FORCES
YOU'RE NOT PREPARED FOR!
WHAT DO YOU THINK A DEMON WOULD'VE
DONE TO YOU?! SHARE HIS LAB NOTES?!
Stupid... well--
DON'T LOOK AT ME!
Okay...
Demon-summoning idiots...
I didn't even mean to shoot that guy,
but they literally forced my hand.
They shouldn't be surprised. You mess
with the Freeman, this is what happens.
Okay, locked, uh...
Well, what's this?
More black magic, no doubt.
Okay, I'm just going to touch this quick.
[fzzt]
WHOA!
SHIT!
NO!
THOSE BASTARDS DID IT AGAIN!
I'M GONNA KILL THEM!
Wait, no! I've been here before!
Yeah, this makes no sense!
I touched this thing--it's harmless!
Right?
Yeah, nothing.
So, what's going on here?
This is the same thing, right?
Or are they different?
Well, here, I already--
[fzzt]
OOOOH! SHIT!
IT'S A TELEPORTER!
WE INVENTED FUCKING TELEPORTERS!
THE NEW AGE OF MAN BEGINS
WITH ME! AND TELEPORTERS!
Oh, my God! I am dizzy from this!
Or maybe that's because I'm spinning.
I've gotta try it again.
Does this work?
It's orange.
[fzzt]
Ohhh-ho-ho-ho!
So, this is what it's like to be a ninja.
Amazing!
Wonder what the power
source is... or why they hover.
Yeah, I have a lot of questions.
Nice!
Dah!
Like, is this Star Trek-style where
it's transmitting my matter as energy
and reconstructing it on the other end?
Or is it just creating
an exact duplicate of me
and I'm really just committing
suicide over and over?
Hmm.
[fzzt]
Hoo...
No, I don't feel dead,
but am I me or am I Gordon #6?
I might not know the difference.
Well, I should continue either way,
even if that means making
sacrifices for the Greater Gordon.
[fzzt]
I mean, I can't think of a cause
I believe in more than that.
Let's go!
[fzzt]
WhoooaaAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
[crying]
My knees hate me...
Why would they put the
exit point there?
Especially when there are
rotating platforms?
WHY ARE THERE ROTATING PLATFORMS?!
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY'RE NEEDED
FOR THE TELEPORTER BALLS!
THEY'RE ALL OVER THE PLACE!
YEAH, WHAT THE FUCK?!
LOOK AT THIS PLACE!
ALL THAT'S MISSING ARE THE BOBBING
HORSE RIDES AND CALLIOPE MUSIC!
THERE'S NO GOD DAMNED REASON FOR
THIS! WE'VE INVENTED TELEPORTERS!
THAT'S "FUCK YOU, PAY ME!" RESEARCH!
WE DON'T NEED TO PAD OUR COSTS
WITH HIGH-TECH CAROUSELS!
Oh, I get it. It's to
double the experiments,
so if the teleportation doesn't make
you vomit then the platforms will.
Fuck.
[fzzt]
No, not that one again!
Don't drop me!
[fzzt]
Good.
Hey, how does the teleporter
know to teleport just me?
I didn't feel any air moving with me.
[Geiger counter ticking]
Maybe it detects--
Oh, joy! More radiation leaks!
[Geiger counter ticking]
This is a great place for a teleporter junction.
[headcrab crunches]
Ah! Fuck!
Where is it?!
Y'know what? You can die down
there slowly by radiation poisoning.
That works just fine for me. I'm
happy to conserve my ammo.
[door buzzes]
Of course...
All right...
Let's do this.
[fzzt]
Oh. All roads lead to Rome, huh?
Seriously, why do we have so
many radioactive waste problems?
Like, we can't find a better place to put it
out here in the middle of the desert?
[fzzt]
Okay, THIS time, let's do it right.
Whoa, shit...
Yeah, that's a great start...
Okay, now here's to hoping it doesn't
teleport me to just a random green ball.
[fzzt]
Okay...
Yeah, this is a great place
to put that pipe, too.
Maybe I'm expected to
lay flat, spread-eagle,
because that makes as much
sense as anything here.
Oh, these are numbered.
I didn't notice.
[fzzt]
Oh, you again!
Okay, time for dance lessons.
Yeah, one-two...
ah, you losers can't dance.
I don't know why I expected otherwise.
Oh, there's an escape route. Excellent.
Is this a bunker full of provisions?
I'll take canned food, dried... anything.
Hey, wait. I've been here before.
This is the other side of that supply room.
Yeah, this is another one of those
rooms with "creative architecture"
that was designed for giant spiderpeople,
because that's the only kind of person
who would find this layout convenient.
SCIENTIST: Fascinating...
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
YOU THINK WE'RE COOL NOW
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T KILLED YOU, YET?!
YOU HAD TELEPORTERS AND WERE
HOLDING OUT ON ME!
I'M NOT GONNA FORGET THAT!
EVER!
Hey, that's an excellent point:
if we already HAD teleporters,
why the hell was my team even
doing the experiment?!
THERE'S NO POINT TO THE EXPERIMENT
IF TELEPORTERS ALREADY EXIST!
BLAAA-
[fzzt]
--AAAGH!
THAT'S LIKE TESTING FOR TESTING
FOR WATER WHEN IT'S R--
[fzzt]
--AINING!
So, what happened? Did they make
this off OUR research
or were we duplicating work for
no reason at all?!
I THOUGHT WE WERE ALL THE SAME COMPANY!
WHY ARE DIVISIONS BACKSTABBING?!
[fzzt]
ARE WE MICROSOFT?!
I'M SORRY, I THOUGHT I
WORKED AT BLACK MESA!
[fzzt]
Whoa-ho-OH!
WAAAAAAAAH! AAAAAAA--
[fzzt]
--AH!
OH, GOD!
Ah, jeez...
Well...
It looks like momentum from
teleportation is not preserved.
That's helpful, but that raises
so many more questions.  Like--
[fzzt]
--wouldn't my heart stop and
resume beating?
Wouldn't each trip be literally
a small heart attack?
I mean, it would still be worth
it, but what's going on here?
[fzzt]
Yeah, I don't feel it.
No, fuck "6"! Not that one.
This is all that's left.
Oh, wait, wait!
What if this is a trap?
Ohhhh...
Yeah, you wanted to drop
my ass dead, didn't you?
Yeah, this is the Black Mesa I know!
[fzzt]
I'M RIGHT! Now I know
why it's all rotating!
It's teleportation Russian Roulette--
an over-engineered way of proving
you're hardcore. Perfect for scientists.
These are chambers in a gun.
[fzzt]
Wow, that's a big one.
Maybe it knows things.
[door buzzes]
No, that would be too easy.
What's going on here?
[electricity arcing]
Daah!
Whoa, what is--
[teleportation sound]
Hey!
OH, PISS OFF! I CAN TELEPORT, TOO!
[teleportation sound]
Now what?
You're not special anymore!
But this is.
This has the answers.
[fzzt]